[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The mixture of hot cream and melted chocolate is called ganache. What does the French word ganache literally mean in English?", "correct_answer": "fool", "incorrect_answers": ["flower", "chocolate", "cream"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Metal Storm weapons, that can fire tens of thousands of rounds a minute, were developed where?", "correct_answer": "Australia", "incorrect_answers": ["Belgium", "Livermore, California", "Piscatawny, New Jersey"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these are eaten by the Red Fox?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["Insects", "worms", "eggs"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What soft drink brand has the same name as a Native American tribe of Northern California?", "correct_answer": "Shasta", "incorrect_answers": ["Coca-Cola", "RC Cola", "Pespi"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the 1978 movie Grease, Danny Zuko, portrayed by John Travolta, falls in love with an innocent girl from Australia, named Sandy. What was Sandys last name?", "correct_answer": "Olsson", "incorrect_answers": ["Mitchell", "Jones", "It was not revealed"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "For his performance in what movie did Bruce Willis receive his first Golden Globe nomination?", "correct_answer": "In Country", "incorrect_answers": ["Mortal Thoughts", "Die Hard", "Last Man Standing"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "There was a fire in South Dakota that destroyed over 90,000 acres.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "As a child Michael Myers, the character from the Halloween film series, was relatively normal until what age?", "correct_answer": "6", "incorrect_answers": ["8", "14", "11"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which two movies have been nominated for 11 Academy Awards but won none?", "correct_answer": "The Color Purple and The Turning Point", "incorrect_answers": ["Ragtime and The Elephant Man", "Quo Vadis and The Nuns Story", "Peyton Place and The Sand Pebbles"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the name of the spacecraft that entered Saturns orbit in 2004?", "correct_answer": "Cassini", "incorrect_answers": ["Pioneer 11", "Voyager 2", "Galileo"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the name of the beneficial mold that develops on grapes under moist conditions and leaves grape crops partially raisined?", "correct_answer": "noble rot", "incorrect_answers": ["methuselah", "fizzante", "phylloxera"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the following disorders is not of the Endocrine System?", "correct_answer": "Parkinsons Disease", "incorrect_answers": ["Hyperthyroidism", "Diabetes", "Osteoporosis"]}]